<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Science Engineering - Misadventures and Coffee</title>
    <link>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Science Engineering - Misadventures and Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Joshua Arndt 2022 &amp;copy; All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:48:36 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Historical Events That Happened</title>
      <link>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/historical_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:48:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/historical_events/</guid>
      <description>About This Project Depending on how many events are aggregated here, this page could get big. At that point I&amp;rsquo;ll have to make the title collapsible or something. For the time being it will be a scroll-fest.
North America Anything North of the Panama Canal.
1874 Huge Locust Swarm Described in detail at Historynet.com. The geographic scale of the swarm is summarized partway through:
&amp;ldquo;A map produced by the state of Missouri shows that the 1874 infestation spread from the eastern slope of the Rockies into western Iowa, Minnesota and Missouri and from the Canadian Prairie provinces to central Texas, just north of Austin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate The Snake Plant</title>
      <link>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/snake_plant_auto_water/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 11:47:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/snake_plant_auto_water/</guid>
      <description>Scrub The Air Back in the &amp;rsquo;80s NASA conducted studies on plants suitable for &amp;ldquo;Indoor Air Pollution Abatement&amp;rdquo;. The Sansevieria family of plants were excellent performers and have the added benefit of being hardy succulents, requiring little water and indirect sunlight. A living plant is calming in my work space and the added air quality benefit makes this an easy choice for the amount of space it takes.
The Plant The sansevieria fernwood variety happens to be $7 at Ikea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Blackburn</title>
      <link>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/hugo_blackburn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 19:55:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/hugo_blackburn/</guid>
      <description>Preamble This site is a work in progress, a project as such. It has been enough of an effort for me that documenting the details is worthwhile for me, maybe for someone else too.
A statically-generated site allows all of your content to be created and maintained locally and allows you to control display elements with finer granularity.
All of my work and personal computing is and has been on Windows OS machines, for various reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensor Boilerplate</title>
      <link>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/sensor_boilerplate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 12:44:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weightedeights.github.io/projects/sensor_boilerplate/</guid>
      <description>Microcontrollers The Adafruit Feather family of microcontrollers is compact and with loads of useful expansion options. The latest and greatest as of now is the &amp;ldquo;Feather M4 Express&amp;rdquo; powered by the 120MHz ATSAMD51J19. This board ships with CircuitPython, Adafruit&amp;rsquo;s simplified distribution of Micropython, and 2MB of flash for library, script, and data storage. Priced under $25, its a no brainer for anyone and everyone wanting to break into hobby electronics of just about any flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
